Welcome back.
歡迎回來。
In the last section, we made a lot of changes to our layout to improve small screens.
在最後一節中，我們在版面上做了一個很大的變化來加強在小螢幕上的顯示。
Unfortunately, this caused a lot of problems for larger screens.
不幸的是，這在大螢幕上造成了許多的問題。
We're going to go through and make one more round of changes.
我們要面對他並迎接在一輪的改變。
The first problem that we run into is something we almost expected.
我們第一個遇到的問題和我們預想的差不多。
We know that Outlook doesn't support max-width.
我們知道， Outlook不支持最大寬度 。
However, the way we're going to fix it is going to be completely different from before.
然而，我們解決他的方式和以前完全的不一樣。
We know that this problem only occurs in Outlook or clients that use IE as a rendering engine.
我們知道這個問題只有出現在outlook或是以IE為排版引擎的客戶端上。
We're going to create a new conditional comment that
我們要創建一個新的條件註釋
targets Outlook and IE, and applies a table only when those two conditions are met.
專注在outlook和IE上，只將它應用在滿足這兩個條件的表上。
We also need to go outside of our content table and close the table that we created.
需要在我們創建的表格之外關閉他。
While we're only showing you the solution applied to the header,
而我們只針對頁首做教學，
we have to repeat this process for every content container table.
我們需要重複這些過程到每一個內容表單上。
Now we're going to tackle another edge case problem in clients using the Word rendering engine.
現在我們要來解決另一個以Word為排版引擎的客戶端的邊界問題。
When two tables have the value of left on the align attribute,
當兩個表中都有在屬性中設定向右對齊的值，
Word adds extra spacing around each table with border spacing.
Word以邊框間距的方式增加了額外的空白在各個表格上。
This extra spacing makes the two widths larger than their container, so they won't stack properly.
這個額外的間距使得這兩個的寬度都比裝置寬，所以他們並不會正常的堆疊。
This solution is a weird one.
這裡有個奇怪的解決方式。
We're actually going to go back to using two cells to align our columns,
我們要使用兩個單元格來對齊我們的列，
but we're only going to do that when clients are using Microsoft Word,as their rendering engine.
但我們只打算應用在當排版引擎為Microsoft Word時。
Here, we're using a conditional comment
在這裡，我們使用的是條件註釋
to target all of the clients using Microsoft Word using a close cell,
來指定所有以Microsoft Word為排版引擎的客戶端使用封閉單元格，
and then opening another cell to surround our two tables.
然後打開一個單元格來包我們的兩個表格。
Our earlier hack, where we used two divs with display inline block actually created another problem for us.
之前的手段，我們使用兩個div來顯示行內空白，實際上造成了另一個問題。
With our two tables aligned, they would be side by side in our desktop view.
看看我們兩個表的對齊，他們將會以邊界對邊界的方式顯示在電腦桌面。
However, display inline block also adds a little bit of space around a container.
然而，inline-block 也增加了一些空格在裝置上。
The solution for this is, again, very weird.
這情況又有一個怪異解決方式。
What we can do is we can tell those two divs to have a font size of zero.
我們可以做的就是將兩個div的字體大小設定為零。
This will make clients not render that extra space around them,
這將使客戶端無法在他們附近呈現額外的空格
and this won't impact our content styles
且這不會影響我們的文件格式，
because we have all of our styles inline on the table cells nested within them.
因為我們所有內嵌在單元表格的樣式inline
Now we have another edge case problem
現在我們還有另一個邊界問題。
that's specific to one client, but this time it's Yahoo Mail.
這次也是針對特定的客戶端---Yahoo Mail。
Our entire layout is being aligned to the left.
我們的整個排版都向左對齊了。
If we inspect the CSS, like we did before,
如果我們像之前一樣仔細檢查CSS，
we can see that Yahoo is applying margin: 0 to tables.
我們可以發現Yahoo應用 margin: 0 到表格中。
This overrides our align: center.
這覆寫了我們的 align: center。
Since this problem only occurs in Yahoo Mail,
因為這個問題只會出現在Yahoo Mail中，
and Yahoo does support CSS in a style tag,
且Yahoo支援在style tag中的CSS。
we can make our fix in one location.
我們可以讓將其固定在一個位置。
We're going to add CSS that targets tables and set margin: 0 auto with an important declaration.
我們要來添加CSS，用來指定表格且用important來標註margin: 0 auto的設定
This will override Yahoo's CSS.
這將覆蓋Yahoo的CSS。
Our final step is to add our remaining content to the bottom of our email.
我們的最後一步驟就是加入剩下的內容在郵件的底部
This is a repetition of what we've already done,
這其實就是重複我們之前做過的
where we're going to apply our width of 100% and our max width of 600 pixels to each table.
在這裡我們要將每個表格的寬度設定為100%以及最大的寬度是600px。
It's been a long battle, but now our email is
這是一個漫長的戰鬥，但現在你的電子郵件都是好看的
looking great in small-screen clients and large-screen clients,
在大螢幕或是小螢幕
with or without media queries.
有或沒有media queries。
Now it's your turn to make that final round of changes.
現在輪到你來做最後的挑戰了
Chk chk, boom.
CHK CHK ， 繁榮 。
Oh, this is it.
哦 ， 這是它。
Ahem.
啊哈 。
Oh, man, I was ??I almost dropped the mic.
哦 ，伙計 ， 我是 - 我幾乎 放棄了 麥克風 。
Pick it back up like, "Aw, sorry."
撿起來 備份 一樣 ， AW ，對不起 。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I still need that.
我還需要 這一點。